dmtc.com 2017-06-06

# Del Mar Thoroughbred Club Privacy Policy

## Your Privacy Rights

#### We have updated our Privacy Policy

Del Mar Thoroughbred Club continues to embrace a larger digital presence in order to provide our fans and customers more products and services designed to enhance enjoyment of the Del Mar experience and the sport of thoroughbred racing. By making changes to our digital presence, our Privacy Policy has been updated and this new Privacy Policy is effective on August 8,2014.

### Our Privacy Policy

This website is owned and operated by Del Mar Thoroughbred Club (“DMTC”), a California corporation with its principal place of business located at 2260 Jimmy Durante Boulevard, Del Mar, California 92014. The following guidelines disclose the privacy policies for this website and includes any DMTC affiliated website accessed via the Internet, mobile or other devices, and applications and sites affiliated with DMTC’s products or services, including, but not limited to, www.dmtc.com, www.delmarscene.com; “My Del Mar”, DMTC’s online gift shop and ticket office, “Del Mar Mobile” and https://statements.dmtc.com (collectively, the “Online Services”).

We respect your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This privacy statement explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of personal information provided to us when you register for a "My Del Mar" account or otherwise provide such information to us in connection with any of our Online Services. The terms of this privacy statement apply to information collected from you, unless different terms are specified as part of a special offer, or in another form or contract we provide to you and you consent to those terms by participating in such special offer or program, or otherwise.

#### What is personal information?

Personal information is information that identifies an individual or is directly associated with a specific person or entity. Examples are a customer's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, or information about activities which can be directly linked to that person, such as purchases that he or she may make. In our view, personal information does not include data that we may collect about a group or category of our products, services or customers, from which specific customer identities have been removed. Information that is aggregated in this way may enable us to take information about how you may use a service and combine that with information about how others use the same service, but with no personal information included in the resulting data. Such aggregated data can help us understand trends and needs of our customers so that we can better consider new services and tailor those we have to better meet our customers' desires.

#### How do we collect personal information?

We collect personal information about you when you sign up for and create a "My Del Mar" profile, place an order through our gift shop of ticket office, or sign up for an on track contest or promotion or sign up for and create a profile through our Del Mar Mobile application, and use any of the foregoing services.

Certain cookies are saved on your computer to help our web server remember who you are, and your viewing and logging-in preferences.

#### How do we use the personal information we collect from you?

The personal information we collect is generally used to tell you about opportunities and events that may be of interest to you.

If you prefer not to receive information from us, you can let us know that by modifying your online profile or by clicking on a link provided specifically for opting-out of all lists that is placed at the footer of emails sent out.

#### Do we share your personal information?

We do not sell, rent, share or disclose personal information to third parties without your prior consent, except in the following limited circumstances.

If you order something from us, such as through Silks Gift Shop, we may provide to a third party information that is necessary to complete your order. For example, we may provide your address to a shipping carrier, and if you pay by a credit card or debit card, your card number and sales transaction information are passed on to the card processor and/or issuer (including their service providers such as fraud verification services).

Also, we may disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process or authorities, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, personal property or safety of DMTC, our customers, employees or the public.

DMTC may contract with other companies to provide certain services on its behalf, including billing processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, list processing and analytics or promotions management. Under such circumstances, DMTC shall only provide such third party with the relevant information required to perform their services. These service providers are restricted from using any data received from DMTC for their own marketing purposes.

#### What do we do to protect personal information?

We have put into place various security measures in an effort to protect personal information from loss, misuse or alteration while it is under our control. Personal information we collect is stored electronically and may be combined with other information you give us.

Account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To protect confidentiality of personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person.

#### What about links to other web sites?

Our Online Services feature links to websites of third parties who have agreed to offer goods and services to our customers. This privacy policy applies only to our Online Services. Any personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is subject to that third party's privacy policy and practices. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of websites to which we link. We encourage you to learn about their privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with personal information.

#### What if you want to update, review or correct personal information?

You may update, review or correct your online account information at any time online by accessing your password-protected profile via the "My Del Mar" area of our website.

#### What if you want to opt-out, correct or cancel personal information?

E-mail: Upon registration for our Online Services, you may have the opportunity to set your preferences to receive e-mails regarding service updates, newsletters or product or service promotions. Any recipient of e-mail notices may opt out of receiving them at any time. To opt out of receiving e-mails, please email your request to customerservice@dmtc.com or follow the unsubscribe instructions located near the bottom of each service update, newsletter or promotional e-mail.

Corrections/Cancellations. If your personal information is incorrect, DMTC will correct such information upon your request. Please email your correction to customerservice@dmtc.com. Upon request, DMTC will cancel your registration, thereby removing you and your personal information from our DMTC database. Please direct your request to customerservice@dmtc.com.

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents may opt-out of DMTC’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, any California resident may choose to opt-out of the sharing of such personal information with third parties for marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request in writing to the DMTC Customer Service mailing address set forth below or by directing such request to customerservice@dmtc.com. For the avoidance of doubt, it is important to understand that this opt-out shall not prohibit any disclosure made for non-marketing purposes.

If you would like to mail your request to us, please direct it to:

> Del Mar Thoroughbred Club Customer Service  
>  P.O. Box 700  
>  Del Mar, CA 92014 

#### How do we notify you if we change our privacy statement?

We reserve the right to change this privacy statement at any time. We will alert you to the fact that changes have been made by indicating at the top of the privacy statement the date that it was last updated. We encourage you to review our privacy statement to make sure you understand how information you provide will be used.
